Andrew Young

Shipping and Receiving Lead - Kings Peak Manufacturing

Eden, UT 84310 Andrewyoung4@mail.weber.edu 801.710.8829

I am a hard working individual with many years of CNA experience under my belt. Throughout those years I have gained many skills when it comes to customer service, data entry, and time management. I am a great multitasker and have the ability to work well under pressure. I invest myself greatly when it comes to my job whatever the position may be and I am a great team player. Finally I am willing to step up to leadership roles or positions if need be.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Full Stack Development Bootcamp

University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UT October 2019 to Present

A six month full stack web development bootcamp through the University of Utah. The course teaches many programming languages and useful libraries including: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Node, MongoDB, and React. The course comes complete with a certificate at the end of the program showing proficiency in full stack web development.

Patient Relations Specialist

University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UT May 2019 to Present

Checking patients in for their appointments, scheduling patients for future appointments, greeting patients as they arrive, adding and verifying insurance to the patient's medical record, answering the phones promptly giving the patient the necessary information they require.

Shipping and Receiving Lead

Kings Peak Manufacturing - Pleasant View, UT June 2018 to Present

Shipping and receiving of aerospace parts and raw materials. Clerical duties including use of all aspects of Microsoft office as well as organizing and ensuring a smooth flow of confidential documentation, and government contracts through their proper processes. Organizational skills include finding issues within our system and fixing them before then can become an issue, completing and filing paperwork, and organization of the warehouse.

CNA/Therapy aide

Pineview Transitional Rehab - South Ogden, UT June 2017 to April 2018

General customer service as well as assisting geriatric patients with their activities of daily living, assisting certified physical therapists to rehabilitate patients, charting patient vitals and general patient information.

CNA/Medical Technician

StoneyBrooke - Eden, UT June 2016 to May 2017

General customer service as well as assisting geriatric patients with their activities of daily living, handing out medications under the supervision of a nurse and charting vital signs and general patient information.

CNA - Certified Nursing Assistant

The Gables of Brigham City - Brigham City, UT August 2015 to May 2016

General customer service as well as assisting geriatric patients with their activities of daily living and charting vital signs as well and general patient information.

CNA - Certified Nursing Assistant

Willowglen Health and Rehab - Brigham City, UT January 2015 to August 2015

General customer service as well as assisting geriatric patients with their activities of daily living and charting patient vitals and patient information.

Education

Computer Science

Weber State University - Ogden, UT January 2017 to Present

General Studies

University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UT August 2016 to January 2017

High school or equivalent

Skills

- Data Entry (4 years)
- Customer Service (3 years)
- Multi Tasking (4 years)
- Organizational Skills (4 years)